NELLI MAINS

SKILLS

UiPath · Nice · BI Tools · Database ·

RPA Blue Prism · Business Trends ·

Automation Anywhere · SCRUM

EDUCATION

BA in Economics and Business Unicaf University

0000 0040

New York, NY

STRENGTHS



Knowledgeable Decision-Making

Analyzing Process Maturity Models and business organizational structures to forecast and maximize ROI and profit margins by 55%. Providing data-oriented solutions to senior management when taking business-crucial decisions.

Business Trends

Ability to predicts gaps within business strategy and potential pressure points by overseeing the impact of local and national trends on the economy. Integrating RPA solutions to tackle and maximize efficiency.

Documentation

Highly experienced in preparing various reports, PDD (process description document), SDD (solution design document) to enhance the understanding of the provided solutions by a 75% AVG.

RPA Business Analyst: Simplyifing Business Processes with Automation and PMM

\$\ +1-715-156-2618 @ elonmusk@fakemail.com \$\alpha\$ linkedin.com/in/nelliemains3 \$\ Dallas, TX\$

SUMMARY

RPA Business Analyst with 10+ years of experience in creating platforms for business-crucial decisions with automated systems and business data. Innovating companies with RPA solutions to increase the rate, standard, and productivity of work by 85%. Analyzing huge data (and data systems) to accelerate business operations and lower costs by an AVG of \$35K/ year. Experienced in preparing detailed and systematized reports with an outlook on the whole business model and operations to visualize how crucial decisions could impact the future of the organization.

EXPERIENCE

RPA Business Analyst

2017 - Ongoing

Hudson PLC

Dallas, TX

Hudson PLC is mainly focused on audience based programmatic display marketing.

- Closely monitoring business processes to integrate RPA to enhance the overall productivity by 65%
- Strategizing with all 12+ departments to better understand their specific needs and align them with business strategy with RPA solutions
- Presenting 4+ annual reports to key stakeholders, detailing successful integrations; tests
 and reviews; and assisting them to take business-crucial decisions to increase the positive
 ROI (by an AVG of \$35K/ year)

Business Analyst

2014 - 2017

Keeling Group

Portland, ME

Keeling Group is a national telecommunications company, specialized in deploying regional networks.

- Achieved 50% increase in data retrieval performance by optimizing the SQL queries
- Working together with the marketing and sales departments to assess potential new markets, resulting in 25 new customers and decreasing acquisition costs by 25%
- Provided key stakeholders with reports on current market trends to help them understand
 the impact of the economy on their own business model and how they could avoid
 potential budget deficits

Business Analyst Intern

2012 - 2014

Streich

Manhattan, NY

Streich is the global leader in cloud-based sales, marketing, learning, and customer experience solutions.

- Helped 5 senior business analysts with data management by integrating various automation in Excel - enhancing productivity by 45%
- Prepared 12+ reports for 3 different clients with a focus on understanding pressure points within the business model
- Prepared 3 company-wide guides to improve different departments' understanding of the role of the business analysts by 65%

